[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "You think he's arrogant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "I think it's an indispensable relationship, that's how I would put it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "How important are we in the scheme of things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "How do you think he's doing as president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "I think he's a great president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Now, if that had happened now or on any presidential visit that I was involved in or now is happening, the slick second- nature of these visits, if anything goes wrong like that, there would be a national outcry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Did you ever do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "-- the Americans were calling --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "When you had President Bush?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "-- the Americans were calling the tunes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Were President Bush and you ever around a piano?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I don't think he would appreciate my singing talents.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["UN"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Was the war in Iraq, given all we now know, was that a mistake, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "No, I don't think so, but I think you've got to distinguish between the rightness of the case -- and, of course, the UN and the whole world supported the rightness of the case -- and then the follow-through.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Is part of the special relationship between Britain and America connected to the royal family, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I think the royal family is incredibly popular in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Why do you think Americans are so fascinated by the British royal family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I think it's about Britain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Princess Diana"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "When you saw what happened to Princess Diana, who you knew -- and I knew, for that matter -- and we saw the attention that she got and the relentlessness of it, leading to the terrible event of her death, do you worry about the attention, now, on William and Kate, these new superstars of the British royal family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I think it was a tragedy what happened to Princess Diana.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana", "Kate"], "LOCATION": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Did you get that sense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I think that was important, but I think you've got to look forward, as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IMF"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "When you think about the IMF for a moment, how important is the IMF to the global economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "You see, for 50 years, the IMF was dealing with national problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IMF", "IMF"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "-- since the financial crisis?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Very important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Why don't you take over the IMF?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "I'm way beyond all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IMF"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Way beyond it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, I was in charge of --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "If you were offered the job, would you take it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I don't think it comes to that, to be honest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, I think we've got these big problems that require people to take a longer-term view than just their own selfish individual or national interest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Has the Internet eroded political power in the conventional sense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Yes and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Burma", "Zimbabwe", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "So, you're seeing, now, people power, driven from the floor up, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "It's because of the Internet that we know about events in Burma, we knew about the fraud elections in Zimbabwe, we knew about many different things that were going on in Egypt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Is it the end of despotic rule as we know it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I think foreign policy cannot be conducted by a few elites that just talk to each other and never consult the public.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Were you surprised when you heard that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "No, because Pakistan is the epicenter of terrorism.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Do you think anybody at high level in Pakistan would've known that Osama bin Laden was there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "The question in Pakistan is, you've got the army, you've got the security services, you've got the politicians, you've got the business class.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan", "Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "And finally, what do you miss most about being prime minister?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJS", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I can tell you what I don't miss.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last one year"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "How would you describe the relationship as it stands?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "There certainly is a trust deficit, but it has been persisting since the last one year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Do you accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "To an extent, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Is it credible that no one else in that base, in all this time, would have had any idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Well, that's a very -- when you say I worked there -- no, I was trained there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What I'm suggesting is does it seem likely to you, with all these military intelligence people around this compound, that nobody knew anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "There's normal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Would you have been happy about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "How would you have reacted if you had been Pakistan's president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Well, I would have certainly reacted, very angrily.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Is it, therefore, illegal what the Americans did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "WP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "It is absolutely illegal, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "So it was an unlawful assassination?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Now you are getting into the legality of -- he was a world class risk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Is that what you are saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan", "Pakistan"]}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Why, if you are President Obama, could you possibly take the risk under those circumstances of not acting unilaterally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well, no Pakistani and no leader in Pakistan will allow this as a justification for any intrusion into Pakistan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "You think he was arrogant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Would you see another raid by the Americans to get rid of another al Qaeda terrorist in exactly the same circumstances, without informing the Pakistani government -- would that be an act of war?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ":", "MD", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Theoretically, technically, yes, indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Will you consider doing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Yes, I have already taken a decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Do you believe you can win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Well, I have entered into politics because I do believe I can win.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Are you worried that if you ramp up the rhetoric over the search for the terrorists in Pakistan against the Americans, they might respond and say, we're yanking our money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Well, first of all, I didn't say act of war.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Do you believe the current Pakistani administration has been 100% honest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100%"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "You mean you would have traded the information that you had bin Laden?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "I would have done something to turn the tables in my favor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "You wouldn't have just handed him over to the Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Wouldn't that be the responsible thing to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I would have used this card to my favor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "If you had known for a fact where bin Laden was, would you have handed him over to America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Let's not get into the details of something which didn't happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110526pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "If you go back into power and you become president again, and you discover that a senior member of al Qaeda, who has without any doubt been committing atrocities, is living in another compound near Karachi or somewhere, would you tell the Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "USHARRAF: I would like to take action.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Qaeda", "Karachi"]}}]